<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BottomNavigationExample</string>
    <string name="title_start">Start</string>
    <string name="title_BMI">BMI</string>
    <string name="title_calories">Kalorie</string>
    <string name="enter_weight">Enter Weight</string>
    <string name="enter_height">Enter Height</string>
    <string name="bmi">BMI</string>
    <string name="enter_age">Enter your age </string>
    <string name="Energy_Burn">Energy Burn</string>
    <string name="Male">Mężczyzna: </string>
    <string name="Female">Kobieta: </string>
    <string name="paragraph1">1 tbls vegetable oil

1 lb boneless skinless chicken breast, cut into 1-inch pieces

2 garlic cloves, finely chopped

2 tsps gingerroot, finely chopped

1 medium onion,  orange quote icon scrubbed with clean vegetable brush under running water and cut into thin wedges

1 cup baby carrots, orange quote icon scrubbed with clean vegetable brush under running and cut lengthwise in half
1 cup chicken broth soup
3 tbls soy sauce
2 tsps sugar
2 cups broccoli flowerets orange quote icon gently rubbed under cold running water
1 cup (3 ounces) fresh mushrooms orange quote icon gently rubbed under cold running water and diced
    Cook the bacon pieces in a large sauce pan over medium heat for 5 minutes.  orange quote icon Wash hands with soap and water after handling bacon.
Add onion to sauce pan with the bacon; sauté until translucent, about 5 minutes. Add green beans and potatoes to the sauce pan with just enough water to cover.
Bring to a boil, then reduce the heat to low. Add salt and pepper and cover. Simmer about 1 hour or until the beans are tender. Stir occasionally and add more water if necessary to keep the beans covered.




1 lb boneless skinless chicken breast, cut into 1-inch pieces

2 garlic cloves, finely chopped

2 tsps gingerroot, finely chopped

1 medium onion,  orange quote icon scrubbed with clean vegetable brush under running water and cut into thin wedges
1 cup baby carrots, orange quote icon scrubbed with clean vegetable brush under running and cut lengthwise in half
1 cup chicken broth soup
3 tbls soy sauce
2 tsps sugar
2 cups broccoli flowerets orange quote icon gently rubbed under cold running water
1 cup (3 ounces) fresh mushrooms orange quote icon gently rubbed under cold running water and diced
½ cup red bell pepper orange quote icon scrubbed with clean vegetable brush under running water and diced
2 tsps cornstarch
4 cups hot cooked Chinese plain noodles</string>
    <string name="title_recipes">Przepisy</string>
</resources>